<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>DonzStory</title>
    <subtitle>Before I leave this world, Please let me tell my own story</subtitle>
    <link href="https://d0n2.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="https://d0n2.in"/>
    <updated>2025-05-28T13:50:37.611Z</updated>
    <id>https://d0n2.in</id>
    <author>
        <name>DonzStory</name>
    </author>
    <generator uri="https://bbg.nekomoe.xyz">Baiyuanneko's Blog Generator</generator>
    <entry>
      <title>Traumgespräch</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=Traumgespräch.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=Traumgespräch.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>I am deeply envious of everyone here because I have no talent. Unlike all of you—you who are talented, who have pursuits, who have dreams—I have no talent at all. In every way, I am inferior to others; I have no dreams. I merely pretend to be competent in certain areas, but a counterfeit is ultimately a counterfeit; it can never become the real thing. I may have told you that some people are fools, but that&amp;#39;s because I believe you shouldn&amp;#39;t waste your own talents and abilities. This is merely the envy and jealousy of a loser toward those who are capable. A capable person shouldn&amp;#39;t abandon their own strengths; if you see them as a burden, isn&amp;#39;t that too extravagant? You simply don&amp;#39;t understand how empty life is without bearing any expectations!</p>


        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2025-05-28T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2025-05-28T13:43:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Out Of Reach</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PensieriOutOfReach.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PensieriOutOfReach.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <p><strong>OutOfReach</strong>  </p>
<p>So, you all are truly remarkable.<br>Perhaps they are peaks I may never reach in my lifetime.<br>As a mere &amp;quot;exam-taker,&amp;quot; what qualifications do I have to be mentioned in the same breath as you?<br>I can only sit daily at the bottom of my dim, damp, and deep well. Then, I look up at you shining stars in the sky.<br>Those are the boundless seas and skies I yearn for in my heart but can never touch.<br>Chairman Mao once said, &amp;quot;Our journey is to the stars and seas.&amp;quot; But you are the dazzling stars on the horizon. As for me, someone like me, a creature of the dark and damp, can only sit at the bottom of the well. To reach even the edge of your brilliance, I&amp;#39;d need to cross the entire Milky Way.<br>Yet, this is beyond my reach.<br><img src="https://fastly.jsdelivr.net/gh/yangdongstation/picd0n2@master/OutOfReach1.png" alt="out of reach"></p>
<p>There&amp;#39;s this image: you are the tip of the pyramid, while I am at the base. No matter how fiercely I compete, no matter how many ladders I raise to climb upward, I can only reach the edge of a cliff. One step forward, and I&amp;#39;d shatter into pieces.<br>After a lifetime of striving, I realize that those who once shared a table with me are unattainable. Even after climbing countless mountains, crossing vast oceans, and exhausting myself in cutthroat competition, I still can&amp;#39;t catch a glimpse of their shadows. As a child, I thought I could reach for the moon in the heavens. Now I know that even if I ascended to the heavens, I couldn&amp;#39;t touch the moon&amp;#39;s edge—only gaze in vain, mocking my own futile arrogance like a mayfly shaking a great tree.<br>Your achievements make me look up in awe, unattainable as high mountains. My efforts are like the bird Jingwei trying to fill the sea—unless aided by immortals, they&amp;#39;re doomed like Kuafu chasing the sun, destined to vanish in the crowd… My endeavors are like ants trying to shake trees… My &amp;quot;Yu Gong&amp;quot; (Foolish Old Man) efforts… Unless a Hercules assists, they&amp;#39;ll be seen as the madness of a lunatic. All my toil is but futile, wasted labor.<br>The achievements I pursue are but illusory reflections in water or flowers in a mirror. Like a drug-addled German Third Reich officer, who thinks he can stay awake for three days straight, feeling omnipotent—only a hallucination of morphine and heroin before the final flicker of life, a castle in the air.<br>Like in <em>The Kite Runner</em>, after Hassan and Amir finished playing, Amir returned to his palace, while Hassan went back to his thatched hut—they were never of the same world. Tragically, I&amp;#39;m not even as fortunate as Hassan. I have no hut to return to, no safe harbor… So I envy everyone.  </p>
<p>Alright… I&amp;#39;ll go make my futile efforts, to feel like I&amp;#39;m doing something real instead of chasing illusory dreams. Sometimes we numb ourselves—whether life is unsatisfying, days are too hard, or family traumas linger—using smoke, alcohol, dexmedetomidine, or pregabalin. It doesn&amp;#39;t matter; what I do… is just like these things, a way to detach from reality, to stop feeling so unfulfilled.</p>


        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2025-02-27T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2025-02-27T08:01:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Summary in 2022, Outlook to 2023</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=SummaryIn2022OutlookTo2023.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=SummaryIn2022OutlookTo2023.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          Summary in 2022, Outlook to 2023

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html">Summary in 2022, Outlook to 2023</summary>
      <updated>2023-01-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2023-01-01T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Before All</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=BeforeALL.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=BeforeALL.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          Before All

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html">Before All</summary>
      <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Night</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=Night.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=Night.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Dawn</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=dawn.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=dawn.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Polar Night I</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-I.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-I.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Polar Night II</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-II.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-II.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry></feed>