<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>DonzStory</title>
    <subtitle>Before I leave this world, Please let me tell my own story</subtitle>
    <link href="https://d0n2.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="https://d0n2.in"/>
    <updated>2025-02-27T08:27:07.443Z</updated>
    <id>https://d0n2.in</id>
    <author>
        <name>DonzStory</name>
    </author>
    <generator uri="https://bbg.nekomoe.xyz">Baiyuanneko's Blog Generator</generator>
    <entry>
      <title>Out Of Reach</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PensieriOutOfReach.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PensieriOutOfReach.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <p><strong>OutOfReach</strong>  </p>
<p>So, you all are truly remarkable.<br>Perhaps they are peaks I may never reach in my lifetime.<br>As a mere &amp;quot;exam-taker,&amp;quot; what qualifications do I have to be mentioned in the same breath as you?<br>I can only sit daily at the bottom of my dim, damp, and deep well. Then, I look up at you shining stars in the sky.<br>Those are the boundless seas and skies I yearn for in my heart but can never touch.<br>Chairman Mao once said, &amp;quot;Our journey is to the stars and seas.&amp;quot; But you are the dazzling stars on the horizon. As for me, someone like me, a creature of the dark and damp, can only sit at the bottom of the well. To reach even the edge of your brilliance, I&amp;#39;d need to cross the entire Milky Way.<br>Yet, this is beyond my reach.<br><img src="https://fastly.jsdelivr.net/gh/yangdongstation/picd0n2@master/OutOfReach1.png" alt="out of reach"></p>
<p>There&amp;#39;s this image: you are the tip of the pyramid, while I am at the base. No matter how fiercely I compete, no matter how many ladders I raise to climb upward, I can only reach the edge of a cliff. One step forward, and I&amp;#39;d shatter into pieces.<br>After a lifetime of striving, I realize that those who once shared a table with me are unattainable. Even after climbing countless mountains, crossing vast oceans, and exhausting myself in cutthroat competition, I still can&amp;#39;t catch a glimpse of their shadows. As a child, I thought I could reach for the moon in the heavens. Now I know that even if I ascended to the heavens, I couldn&amp;#39;t touch the moon&amp;#39;s edge—only gaze in vain, mocking my own futile arrogance like a mayfly shaking a great tree.<br>Your achievements make me look up in awe, unattainable as high mountains. My efforts are like the bird Jingwei trying to fill the sea—unless aided by immortals, they&amp;#39;re doomed like Kuafu chasing the sun, destined to vanish in the crowd… My endeavors are like ants trying to shake trees… My &amp;quot;Yu Gong&amp;quot; (Foolish Old Man) efforts… Unless a Hercules assists, they&amp;#39;ll be seen as the madness of a lunatic. All my toil is but futile, wasted labor.<br>The achievements I pursue are but illusory reflections in water or flowers in a mirror. Like a drug-addled German Third Reich officer, who thinks he can stay awake for three days straight, feeling omnipotent—only a hallucination of morphine and heroin before the final flicker of life, a castle in the air.<br>Like in <em>The Kite Runner</em>, after Hassan and Amir finished playing, Amir returned to his palace, while Hassan went back to his thatched hut—they were never of the same world. Tragically, I&amp;#39;m not even as fortunate as Hassan. I have no hut to return to, no safe harbor… So I envy everyone.  </p>
<p>Alright… I&amp;#39;ll go make my futile efforts, to feel like I&amp;#39;m doing something real instead of chasing illusory dreams. Sometimes we numb ourselves—whether life is unsatisfying, days are too hard, or family traumas linger—using smoke, alcohol, dexmedetomidine, or pregabalin. It doesn&amp;#39;t matter; what I do… is just like these things, a way to detach from reality, to stop feeling so unfulfilled.</p>


        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2025-02-27T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2025-02-27T08:01:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Summary in 2022, Outlook to 2023</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=SummaryIn2022OutlookTo2023.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=SummaryIn2022OutlookTo2023.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>About... 200 days ago I made one of the most important decisions of my life. I may not regret my decision, but I definitely regret all the avoidances I made, hopefully it&amp;#39;s not too late.
Afterglow is a cup of boiled orange water, shallowly poured on the wind chimes in the window, the wind knocked over the glass of the sun, and the warm yellow fragrance spread all over the room. It seems that the intermittent separation in the past few years is nothing but the plot of the dream. But the plots in dreams and fantasies are slowly approaching me, approaching, approaching, and finally, they merged with me, and I finally chose to be the self in my dream. That&amp;#39;s right, the self that only existed in imagination before... I never hid my tendencies, but... I was always intimidated by all kinds of side effects, and I didn&amp;#39;t dare to take a step forward. I hated the withdrawn self... But until nothing There was no way to retreat, so I decided to move forward from now on. October 23, 2013 was a memorable day. I tried to take my first step...even if I retreated. But time will not wait for me... It will be 2022 in a blink of an eye, and I will be seventeen years old. I know very well that if I don&amp;#39;t move forward, I will regret it for the rest of my life. I have to do everything as soon as possible... Otherwise, everything will become very difficult if I walk this road again.</p>
<p>Time, time, time, it&amp;#39;s so important.</p>
<p>Sometimes I feel that the changes that happen to me are like a game of cultivation. EQ and mental age are cleared when we take this step, and slowly add up again. The forearm is becoming softer and softer, and the curves of the body are becoming more and more obvious.</p>
<p>Recently, the state of study is indeed quite poor. After all, I am locked in my small room of 20 square meters 24 hours a day, and I am still arguing with my parents... I can&amp;#39;t study hard at all... and my mental state is getting worse and worse.</p>
<p>As my sister said, I seem to have become more naive. Looking back, I can always find that I seemed to have done stupid things a few days ago...and then regretted it...and my memory gradually blurred before the choice, it seems that in 2022 I only spent six months... 200 days... so my 2022 is only six months~</p>
<p>2023, I’m so nervous, a lot of things are a cliff that I can’t go wrong, study, family, money, independence, oh, I can’t breathe when I think about it… If I take a wrong step, maybe… I won’t necessarily die, although It is possible, but it will definitely be worse than death...</p>
<p>​My sister told me that out of her selfishness, she hoped that I could be happy every day...
I&amp;#39;m sorry, I didn&amp;#39;t do this kind of thing, I&amp;#39;m not a competent little sister...
​…</p>
<p>Hey, so many people who are so important to me stay in 2022 forever... It seems to leave with them... Hey...
There are many more stars in the sky
But out of personal selfishness, I really don&amp;#39;t want more people to leave me in that form...</p>


        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html">Summary in 2022, Outlook to 2023</summary>
      <updated>2023-01-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2023-01-01T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Before All</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=BeforeALL.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=BeforeALL.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          Before All

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html">Before All</summary>
      <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Night</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=Night.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=Night.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Dawn</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=dawn.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=dawn.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Polar Night I</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-I.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-I.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry><entry>
      <title>Polar Night II</title>
      <link href="https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-II.md"/>
      <id>https://d0n2.in/index.html?type=article&amp;filename=PolarNight-II.md</id>
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          

        ]]>
      </content>
      <summary type="html"></summary>
      <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
      <published>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</published>
      </entry></feed>